### CONTACT ME

in linkedin.com/in/ayelen-garcía-595457232/

ayelengarcia7@gmail.com

+54 91 124979403

### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Ayelen, I'm 29 years old and I'm a former Psychology student. I studied Psychology at the University of Buenos Aires (UBA) for some time. In July this year I started studying Frontend React in the CoderHouse Academy.

I consider myself an employee who gets the job done and gives 100% of herself. I have a strong work ethic and attention to detail. I am also a great teamplayer and I work well in teams as well as individually. Regarding my personality I'm spontaneous, intuitive and creative. I am also a fast learner and I love to learn new things everyday.

I'm searching for my first work experience in the IT field. I am highly motivated and would like to pursue a career path in this field!

# MY SKILLS





**FIGMA** 



CSS



GIT



JAVA SCRIPT



GIT HUB



**ILUSTRATOR** 





BOOSTRAP

### REPOSITORY

Look my proyects!



github.com/ayelengarcia

# AYELEN GARCIA

### FRONT END DEVELOPER - STUDENT

## **EDUCATION**

2022

#### Front end Developer React Js

Coder House - En curso

- Web develop Finish
- Java Script Finish
- React In progress

2018

#### Degree Psychology

University of Buenos Aires. 2018 - 2022

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### School Integrative & Therapeutic companion

March 2020 - September 2022

- ARABELA SRL mar. 2022 sept. 2022 · 7 months
- Team Adip RRHH sept. 2021 mar. 2022 · 7 months
- Asociation "Niños del Sur" (ANSUR) -mar. 2020 mar. 2021 · 1 year 1 month
   .Therapeutic accompaniment with children and adolescents.

  Mental health and accessibility.

#### **Customer Service**

november 2018 - december 2020

• Library & Buffet - University of Psychology - 2 years 2 months Shift responsable, customer service, management tasks administration and finance.

### **ADDITIONAL**

Social Organization "Barrios de Pie"

Planning and coordination · abr. 2019 - abr. 2021

**University of Buenos Aires** 

Pedagogical workshops, recreation, ESI workshops, problematic consumption, height and weight surveys, mental health. Children, adolescents and adults

**CEP - Psychology Student Center** 

Management and communication · abr. 2019 - mar. 2021

**University of Buenos Aires** 

Coordination and management of groups and activities. Communication planning and social networks. Practices in neighborhoods and academic workshops.

## LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Lower Intermediate - Read /Write